const QuestionsArray = [
    {
        id: 1,
        category: 'Geography',
        question: 'What is the captial of Illinois?',
        a1: 'Springfield',
        a2: 'Chicago',
        a3: 'Peoria',
        a4: 'Rockford',
        answer: 1
        
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        category: 'Geography',
        question: 'What is the captial of Florida?',
        a1: 'Orlando',
        a2: 'Tampa',
        a3: 'Tallahasse',
        a4: 'Miami',
        answer: 3
       
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        category: 'Geography',
        question: 'Which Continent is in all four hemispheres?',
        a1: 'Africa',
        a2: 'Australia',
        a3: 'N. America',
        a4: 'Europe',
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        category: 'Geography',
        question: 'How many large islands make up Hawaii?',
        a1: 'Ten',
        a2: 'Eight',
        a3: 'Four',
        a4: 'Five',
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        category: 'History',
        question: 'In what year did JFK die?',
        answer: '1963',
        choices: [
            '1969',
            '1964',
            '1970'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        category: 'History',
        question: 'How long was William Harrision President?',
        answer: '32 days',
        choices: [
            '4 years',
            '8 years',
            '7 months'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        category: 'History',
        question: 'Which of these states did not seceded to form the original Confederacy during the U.S, Civil War?',
        answer: 'Kentucky',
        choices: [
            'Florida',
            'Texas',
            'South Carolina'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        category: 'History',
        question: 'The ancient city of Rome was built on how many hills?',
        answer: 'Seven',
        choices: [
            'Six',
            'Five',
            'Four'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        category: 'Entertainment',
        question: 'What are the dying words of Charles Foster Kane in Citizen Kane?',
        answer: 'Rosebud',
        choices: [
            'Goodbye',
            "I'll miss you",
            'Xanadu'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        category: 'Entertainment',
        question: 'For what movie did Tom Hanks score his first Academy Award nomination?',
        answer: 'Big',
        choices: [
            'Toy Story',
            'Forest Gump',
            'The Green Mile'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        category: 'Entertainment',
        question: 'In Risky Business, what song did Tom Cruise famously lip-sync to in his underwear?',
        answer: '"Old Time Rock and Roll" by Bob Seger',
        choices: [
            '"You Shook Me All Night Long" by AC/DC',
            '"Whip It" by Devo',
            '"Mr. Roboto" by Styx'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        category: 'Entertainment',
        question: 'Alfred Hitchcock famously directed a 1963 horror movie about what type of animal?',
        answer: 'Birds',
        choices: [
            'Wolves',
            'Cicadas',
            'Cats'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        category: 'Science',
        question: 'What is the most abundant gas in the atmosphere?',
        answer: 'Nitrogen',
        choices: [
            'Oxygen',
            'Hydrogen',
            'Carbon'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        category: 'Science',
        question: 'What is the hottest planet in the solar system?',
        answer: 'Venus',
        choices: [
            'Mars',
            'Jupiter',
            'Mercury'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        category: 'Science',
        question: "Whatâ€™s the boiling point of water?",
        answer: '100 degrees C',
        choices: [
            '100 degrees F',
            '32 degrees C',
            '250 degrees F'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        category: 'Science',
        question: 'How long does a human red blood cell survive?',
        answer: '120 days',
        choices: [
            '1 day',
            '60 days',
            '280 days'
        ]
    },

]

export default QuestionsArray